[
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x - 5) + x(x - 5)(x + 5) + (x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^4 - 3*x^3 - 27*x^2 + 105*x - 100"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 4)(x + 2)(x + 3)(x + 5) + x(x + 1)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 7*x^3 - 5*x^2 - 91*x - 120"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x + 4) + x(x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 2)(x + 4) + x(x + 1)(x - 4)(x - 2)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 2*x^4 - 30*x^3 + 53*x^2 + 164*x"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 4)(x + 5) + x(x - 5)(x + 3) + x(x + 1)(x - 1)(x + 2)(x + 4) + x(x - 4)(x - 3)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 6*x^4 + 9*x^3 - 14*x^2 - 2*x + 20"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 5)(x - 2) + x(x - 5)(x - 3)(x + 5) + (x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 3)(x + 3) + (x - 4)(x + 2)(x + 4)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "3*x^4 - x^3 - 42*x^2 + 27*x - 205"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 4) + (x + 1)(x - 5)(x + 4)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 13*x^3 - 5*x^2 - 93*x - 100"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 3)(x - 2) + (x + 1)(x - 2) + x(x + 1)(x + 2)(x + 4) + (x + 1)(x - 4)(x - 3)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 + 6*x^3 - 9*x^2 + 39*x + 64"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 2)(x + 4) + x(x + 1)(x - 5)(x + 3)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 4*x^4 - 21*x^3 - 97*x^2 - 81*x - 8"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 2) + x(x - 2)(x + 3)(x + 5) + x(x + 1)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 + 5*x^3 - 3*x^2 - 18*x + 12"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 1) + x(x - 4)(x - 3)(x + 4)(x + 5) + x(x - 3)(x + 2)(x + 3)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "2*x^5 + 9*x^4 - 30*x^3 - 94*x^2 + 150*x - 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x - 4)(x + 5) + x(x - 1)(x - 5)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^4 - 25*x^2 + 4*x + 20"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 5)(x - 3)(x + 2)(x + 5) + (x - 5)(x + 2)(x + 4)(x + 5) + x(x - 3)(x - 2)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 + 6*x^3 - 53*x^2 - 119*x - 50"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 4)(x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 3) + x(x - 4)(x - 2)",
    "answer": "x^4 - 5*x^3 - 7*x^2 + 62*x - 72"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 2) + x(x - 1)(x - 3)(x + 3)(x + 4) + x(x + 1)(x - 4)(x + 2)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "2*x^5 + 8*x^4 - 31*x^3 - 89*x^2 + 8*x"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x - 4)(x - 3)(x + 3) + x(x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 4)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "2*x^5 - 2*x^4 - 31*x^3 - 3*x^2 + 124*x"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 2)(x + 3) + x(x + 1)(x + 2)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 7*x^3 + 15*x^2 + 13*x + 6"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 2)(x + 3)(x + 4) + (x - 4)(x + 2) + x(x - 1)(x - 4)(x - 3)(x - 2)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 10*x^4 + 36*x^3 - 44*x^2 + 20*x - 32"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 4)(x + 2) + x(x + 1)(x - 5)(x - 3)(x + 5) + (x - 1)(x - 3)(x + 3)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^5 - x^4 - 23*x^3 + 34*x^2 + 31*x + 45"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 5)(x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 3) + (x + 1)(x - 2) + x(x + 1)(x - 5)(x - 4) + (x + 1)(x + 3)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 - 9*x^3 + 2*x^2 + 50*x + 73"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 5)(x + 4) + x(x - 5)(x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 5) + x(x + 1)(x - 3)(x + 3)(x + 4) + x(x + 1)(x - 5)(x - 3)(x - 2)",
    "answer": "3*x^5 - 9*x^4 - 2*x^3 + 81*x^2 - 237*x - 20"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 2)(x + 3) + (x - 3)(x + 5) + x(x - 5)(x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 5) + (x + 1)(x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 5*x^4 - 17*x^3 + 129*x^2 - 175*x + 31"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 5)(x + 3) + x(x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 4*x^3 - 5*x^2 - 29*x - 15"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 4)(x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 2) + x(x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 3)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 6*x^4 - x^3 + 51*x^2 - 63*x"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x - 2)(x + 3)(x + 4) + (x + 1)(x - 5)(x - 3)(x - 2)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 7*x^4 - 6*x^3 - 5*x^2 - 23*x - 30"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 4)(x - 3)(x + 3) + (x - 5)(x - 3)(x + 3)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 - 4*x^3 - 43*x^2 + 36*x + 225"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x - 3) + (x + 1)(x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 3) + x(x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 2) + x(x + 1)(x - 4)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 - 2*x^3 - 19*x^2 + 9*x + 24"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 5) + (x - 1)(x - 2) + (x - 1)(x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 2*x^4 - 21*x^3 - 9*x^2 + 89*x - 38"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x - 3) + (x - 5)(x - 2)(x + 3) + (x + 1)(x + 2)(x + 5) + x(x + 1)(x + 3)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 12*x^3 + 25*x^2 + 18*x + 40"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 4)(x - 3)(x + 5) + x(x - 1)(x + 2) + (x - 3)(x + 3) + (x - 2)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "2*x^3 + x^2 - 22*x + 41"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 2)(x + 4) + (x - 5)(x - 2)(x + 3) + x(x + 1)(x - 3)(x + 3)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 5*x^4 - 3*x^3 - 47*x^2 - 55*x + 30"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 5)(x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 5) + x(x - 5)(x + 3) + x(x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 4) + x(x - 5)(x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "3*x^5 - 12*x^4 - 37*x^3 + 186*x^2 - 191*x"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 2)(x + 3)(x + 4) + x(x - 1)(x - 5)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 6*x^3 - 8*x^2 - 19*x"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 4)(x + 5) + x(x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 3) + x(x - 1)(x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 3) + (x - 1)(x - 3)",
    "answer": "2*x^5 - 10*x^4 - 8*x^3 + 96*x^2 - 81*x - 17"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 3)(x + 2) + x(x + 1)(x - 5)(x - 2)(x + 2)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 4*x^4 - 9*x^3 + 17*x^2 + 19*x - 6"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 4)(x + 5) + x(x + 1)(x - 4)(x + 2)(x + 4) + x(x - 5)(x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "2*x^5 - 4*x^4 - 19*x^3 + 73*x^2 - 172*x"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 4)(x + 2) + (x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 3)(x + 2) + x(x + 3)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^4 + x^3 - x^2 + 8*x + 6"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 2)(x + 4) + (x - 1)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "2*x^2 + 8*x + 5"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 5)(x - 2)(x + 3) + x(x + 1)(x - 5)",
    "answer": "2*x^3 - 8*x^2 - 16*x + 30"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 5)(x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 3) + (x + 1)(x - 2) + (x - 5)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 2*x^4 - 19*x^3 + 10*x^2 + 58*x - 22"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x + 5) + (x - 3)(x - 2) + (x + 1)(x - 5)(x - 3)(x + 2) + (x + 1)(x - 3)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "x^4 - 3*x^3 + x^2 + 20*x + 27"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x - 3)(x + 4)(x + 5) + x(x - 1)(x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 3) + x(x + 4)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "2*x^5 + 7*x^4 - 19*x^3 - 52*x^2 + 92*x"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x + 3)(x + 4)(x + 5) + (x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 4) + (x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 2)(x + 2) + x(x - 5)(x - 2)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "4*x^4 + 2*x^3 + 9*x^2 + 63*x - 32"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 5) + x(x - 5)(x + 4) + x(x - 5)(x + 5) + (x - 1)(x - 3)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "3*x^3 - x^2 - 58*x + 4"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 4)(x + 3) + x(x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 2)",
    "answer": "x^4 - 6*x^3 + x^2 + 28*x"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 4)(x + 2) + (x - 1)(x + 2)(x + 3)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 10*x^3 + 19*x^2 - 9*x - 30"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 2)(x + 3) + (x - 4)(x - 3)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 4*x^4 - 19*x^3 + 47*x^2 + 113*x + 12"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 3) + x(x - 1)(x - 2) + (x - 2)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^4 - x^3 - 15*x^2 + 19*x + 14"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 2)(x + 5) + x(x - 1)(x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 3*x^4 - 13*x^3 + 55*x^2 - 22*x"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 3)(x + 2)(x + 4)(x + 5) + (x + 1)(x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 5) + x(x + 1)(x - 4)(x + 3)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "2*x^5 + 14*x^4 - 8*x^3 - 174*x^2 - 162*x + 40"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 5)(x - 4)(x - 2) + x(x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 4)(x - 2) + x(x - 4)(x + 2)(x + 3)(x + 5) + x(x + 1)(x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "3*x^5 - 4*x^4 - 22*x^3 - 35*x^2 - 10*x - 40"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 4)(x - 3)(x + 4) + (x - 1)(x + 3) + (x - 4)(x - 3)(x + 4) + x(x - 3)(x + 2)",
    "answer": "x^4 - 22*x^2 + 12*x + 93"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 5)(x + 2)(x + 5) + x(x + 1)(x - 5)(x + 4) + (x + 1)(x - 4) + x(x - 1)(x + 2)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 + 3*x^3 - 44*x^2 - 75*x - 4"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 3) + (x - 4)(x - 3)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "2*x^3 - 5*x^2 - 25*x + 66"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 3)(x + 3)(x + 4) + x(x + 1)(x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 4) + (x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 4)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 3*x^4 - 15*x^3 + 49*x^2 + 64*x - 56"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x - 2) + x(x - 3)(x + 2) + x(x - 3)(x + 3)(x + 5) + x(x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 3)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 7*x^4 + 21*x^3 - 3*x^2 - 68*x"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 5) + x(x - 1)(x - 4)(x + 2)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 2*x^4 - 20*x^3 - 27*x^2 + 39*x + 5"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 4) + (x - 5)(x - 4)(x - 3)(x + 2) + x(x - 1)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^4 - 8*x^3 + 22*x^2 + 29*x - 116"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 3)(x + 4)(x + 5) + (x - 5)(x + 3) + x(x - 1)(x + 3) + (x - 4)(x + 2)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 14*x^3 + 52*x^2 + 39*x - 47"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 3) + (x - 5)(x - 4)",
    "answer": "x^4 - 8*x^3 + 15*x^2 - x + 5"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 3) + x(x - 1)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "2*x^3 - 5*x^2 + 18*x - 15"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 5)(x + 2)(x + 3) + (x - 1)(x - 5)(x + 4) + (x + 1)(x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 - 32*x^2 - 40*x + 38"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 3)(x + 4) + x(x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 4) + x(x - 2)(x + 2)",
    "answer": "x^4 - 3*x^3 + 7*x + 12"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 5) + (x - 2)(x + 2)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 6*x^4 + x^3 - 23*x^2 - 20*x - 4"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 5)(x - 2)(x + 4)(x + 5) + x(x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 2)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 - 2*x^3 - 37*x^2 - 34*x + 200"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x + 2)(x + 4) + x(x - 1)(x - 5)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 6*x^3 - 4*x^2 - 3*x"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 5)(x - 4)(x - 3)(x + 4) + x(x + 1)(x - 5)",
    "answer": "x^4 - 7*x^3 - 5*x^2 + 123*x - 240"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x - 4)(x + 5) + (x - 4)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^4 - 20*x^2 + 21*x - 20"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 3)(x + 4) + x(x + 1)(x + 4)(x + 5) + (x + 1)(x - 1)(x + 2) + (x + 1)(x - 4)(x + 3)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 + 17*x^3 + 19*x^2 - 70*x - 62"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x + 4)(x + 5) + (x - 1)(x + 4) + x(x + 1)(x - 4)(x + 4)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 6*x^4 - 10*x^3 - 87*x^2 - 66*x - 24"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x - 5)(x - 2) + (x + 1)(x + 3) + (x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 3) + x(x - 5)(x - 2)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 - 7*x^3 - 23*x^2 + 55*x + 21"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 4)(x - 2) + x(x - 5)(x - 2)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^4 - 3*x^3 - 17*x^2 + 34*x + 8"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 4)(x + 2) + x(x + 1)(x + 2)(x + 4) + x(x - 1)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^5 - x^4 - x^3 + 20*x^2 + 11*x"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 3) + (x - 1)(x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 5) + x(x - 1)(x - 4)(x + 2)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 + 2*x^3 - 18*x^2 - 9*x + 23"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 5)(x + 4) + (x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 3) + x(x - 5)(x - 2)(x + 2)",
    "answer": "x^4 - 4*x^3 - 6*x^2 + 18*x - 17"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 5) + x(x - 4)(x + 2)(x + 3) + x(x - 5)(x - 2)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 + 8*x^3 - 20*x^2 - 38*x - 20"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 2)(x + 4) + (x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 3)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 3*x^4 - 14*x^3 + 45*x^2 - 41*x + 12"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 5)(x - 4)(x - 3)(x - 2) + x(x + 1)(x - 5)(x + 4)(x + 5) + x(x - 1)(x - 3)",
    "answer": "2*x^5 - 9*x^4 + 51*x^3 - 283*x^2 + 23*x"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x + 3) + x(x - 4)(x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 4*x^4 - 19*x^3 + 107*x^2 - 118*x - 3"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 4)(x - 2) + x(x - 5)(x + 2)(x + 3)(x + 4) + (x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 5)(x + 5) + x(x - 4)(x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "2*x^5 + x^4 - 35*x^3 - 45*x^2 - 210*x + 17"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 3)(x + 2)(x + 3) + x(x - 2)(x + 3) + (x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 4)",
    "answer": "3*x^3 - 7*x^2 + 14*x - 38"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 4)(x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 5) + x(x - 1)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^4 - 3*x^3 - 15*x^2 + 101*x - 120"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 1) + (x - 2)(x + 2) + x(x - 5)(x + 3)(x + 4)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 7*x^4 - 13*x^3 - 173*x^2 - 300*x - 5"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 5)(x - 4)(x - 3) + x(x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 5) + (x + 3)(x + 4)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 5*x^4 - 19*x^3 + 125*x^2 - 6*x"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 5)(x - 2)(x + 2) + x(x - 4)(x + 3) + x(x - 1)(x - 4)(x + 3)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 2*x^4 - 17*x^3 - 38*x^2 + 32*x + 20"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x - 4) + (x - 1)(x + 2)(x + 3)(x + 4) + x(x + 1)(x - 5)(x - 4) + x(x + 1)(x - 2)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 + x^3 + 28*x^2 + 11*x - 20"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 3)(x + 4) + (x - 5)(x - 2)",
    "answer": "x^4 + x^3 - 21*x^2 - 23*x + 106"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 2) + x(x + 1)(x - 3)(x - 2)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 5*x^4 - 9*x^3 + 43*x^2 + 46*x"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x - 2) + x(x - 3)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "2*x^3 - x^2 - 11*x"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 4)(x + 5) + (x - 5)(x - 3)(x + 2)(x + 5) + x(x - 1)(x + 2)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 + 5*x^3 - 27*x^2 + 24*x + 170"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 4)(x + 5) + (x - 1)(x + 5) + (x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 2)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 2*x^4 - 28*x^3 + 9*x^2 + 31*x - 15"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 5)(x - 2)(x + 3) + (x - 3)(x + 3) + x(x - 1)(x - 4)(x - 3)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 3*x^4 - 16*x^3 + 50*x^2 - 29*x + 21"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 3)(x + 2)(x + 4)(x + 5) + (x - 5)(x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 5) + x(x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "3*x^4 + 6*x^3 - 18*x^2 + 39*x - 270"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 2) + x(x + 1)(x - 5)(x + 3)(x + 5) + x(x + 1)(x + 2)(x + 3) + x(x + 1)(x - 3)(x + 3)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "2*x^5 + 10*x^4 - 20*x^3 - 141*x^2 - 103*x + 40"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 4)(x + 2)(x + 4)(x + 5) + (x - 3)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 7*x^3 - 5*x^2 - 110*x - 175"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 4) + x(x - 5)(x - 3)(x + 5) + (x - 5)(x - 2)(x + 5) + (x - 5)(x + 2)(x + 3)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 + 3*x^3 - 42*x^2 - 60*x - 86"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 4)(x - 2) + x(x - 3)(x - 2) + (x - 2)(x + 3)(x + 4) + (x + 1)(x - 1)",
    "answer": "3*x^3 - 5*x^2 + 12*x - 25"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x - 2) + x(x - 5)(x + 3) + x(x - 2)(x + 3)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 7*x^3 - 7*x^2 - 37*x"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 3)(x + 3)(x + 4)(x + 5) + x(x + 2)(x + 3)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 10*x^4 + 20*x^3 - 55*x^2 - 156*x"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x - 5)(x + 2)(x + 4) + (x - 5)(x - 2)(x + 3)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 - 50*x^2 - 32*x + 160"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 5) + x(x - 1)(x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^5 - x^4 - 23*x^3 + 41*x^2 + 22*x - 40"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x + 2)(x + 4)(x + 5) + (x - 4)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 12*x^4 + 49*x^3 + 79*x^2 + 39*x - 12"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x + 4)(x + 5) + (x - 4)(x + 3)(x + 4) + x(x - 4)(x + 2)(x + 3) + (x - 1)(x - 5)(x + 2)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 4*x^3 - 5*x^2 - 18*x - 18"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x - 3) + (x - 5)(x - 3)(x + 4)(x + 5) + (x - 3)(x + 2)(x + 3)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 + 8*x^3 - 42*x^2 - 76*x + 228"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x - 3)(x + 3) + x(x - 5)(x + 2)(x + 4)(x + 5) + (x + 4)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 6*x^4 - 16*x^3 - 150*x^2 - 200*x + 29"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 2) + (x - 1)(x + 3)(x + 4)(x + 5) + (x + 1)(x - 2)(x + 2)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 + 8*x^3 + 32*x^2 + 25*x - 64"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x - 3)(x + 2)(x + 3) + (x - 4)(x + 2)(x + 3) + x(x - 1)(x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "2*x^5 - x^4 - 13*x^3 + 8*x^2 - 56*x - 24"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 5)(x + 4)(x + 5) + x(x - 1)(x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 2) + x(x + 1)(x - 4)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 4*x^4 + x^3 + 17*x^2 - 41*x - 100"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 4)(x - 3) + (x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 2)(x + 2) + x(x - 1)(x - 5)(x + 3)(x + 5) + x(x - 5)(x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "2*x^5 - 4*x^4 - 34*x^3 + 58*x^2 - 92*x + 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 5)(x + 4) + x(x + 1)(x - 5)(x - 3)(x + 5) + x(x + 4)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 2*x^4 - 26*x^3 + 58*x^2 + 75*x"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 3)(x + 2) + x(x + 2)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "2*x^3 + 5*x^2 + 2*x"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 5)(x + 2)(x + 3) + (x - 1)(x + 2)(x + 3)(x + 4) + (x - 4)(x - 3)(x + 3)(x + 5) + (x + 2)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "3*x^4 + 9*x^3 - 30*x^2 - 36*x + 162"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x - 4)(x + 4) + (x + 1)(x - 2)(x + 2) + (x - 3)(x + 2)",
    "answer": "2*x^3 + x^2 - 21*x + 6"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 5)(x - 3)(x + 3) + (x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 4)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 - 4*x^3 - 31*x^2 + 36*x + 61"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x + 3)(x + 5) + x(x + 1)(x - 3)(x + 3) + x(x + 1)(x - 5)(x - 2)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 13*x^3 + 20*x^2 + 16*x"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 3)(x + 4)(x + 5) + (x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "2*x^3 + 3*x^2 - 17*x - 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 4)(x - 3) + x(x + 1)(x - 4)",
    "answer": "2*x^3 - 9*x^2 + x + 12"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x - 3)(x + 3) + x(x + 1)(x + 4) + (x + 1)(x + 3)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 3*x^3 + 5*x^2 + 18*x + 15"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 3)(x + 3)(x + 5) + x(x + 2)(x + 3)(x + 4) + x(x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 2)(x + 2)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 4*x^4 + 15*x^3 + 41*x^2 - 41*x"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 5)(x - 3)(x + 3)(x + 4) + x(x - 5)(x + 2)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 29*x^3 - 10*x^2 + 150*x"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 4)(x + 4)(x + 5) + x(x + 1)(x - 4) + (x - 1)(x - 3)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 6*x^3 - 18*x^2 - 88*x + 3"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 2) + x(x - 5)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "x^4 - 3*x^3 - 6*x^2 + x"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 4)(x + 3)(x + 5) + x(x + 1)(x - 5)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 + 4*x^3 - 38*x^2 - 80*x"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 5)(x + 3) + x(x + 1)(x + 3) + (x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 3) + x(x - 1)(x - 4)(x + 3)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 2*x^4 - 16*x^3 - 33*x^2 + 26*x + 24"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 4)(x + 2)(x + 5) + x(x - 3)(x + 3) + x(x - 3)(x - 2) + (x + 1)(x - 1)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "4*x^3 + 3*x^2 - 22*x - 45"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x - 4)(x + 3)(x + 4) + (x - 1)(x - 2)(x + 3)(x + 5) + (x + 2)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 3*x^4 - 14*x^3 - 38*x^2 + 26*x + 40"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x - 2) + x(x + 1)(x - 4)(x + 5) + (x - 5)(x + 3)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 3*x^3 - 15*x^2 - 48*x - 73"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x - 2) + (x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 3)(x + 3) + (x + 4)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^4 - 5*x^3 - 6*x^2 + 65*x - 25"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x - 3)(x + 5) + (x - 5)(x - 3)(x + 2)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 + x^3 - 38*x^2 + 11*x + 120"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 5)(x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 4) + (x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 3)(x + 5) + (x - 4)(x + 2)(x + 4)(x + 5) + x(x - 1)(x - 5)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 4*x^4 + 2*x^3 + 63*x^2 - 254*x - 70"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 4)(x - 3)(x - 2) + (x + 1)(x + 2)(x + 3)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 + 2*x^3 + 67*x^2 + 37*x + 30"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 5)(x + 2) + x(x + 1)(x - 5)(x + 2)",
    "answer": "x^4 - x^3 - 16*x^2 - 20*x"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x + 2) + x(x + 1)(x - 1)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 5*x^3 + 2*x^2 - 2*x"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x + 2)(x + 5) + x(x - 1)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 7*x^3 + 6*x^2 - 14*x"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 5)(x - 3)(x + 4) + x(x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 3) + (x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 4) + x(x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 4)(x + 2)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 18*x^3 - 18*x^2 + 124*x - 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 5) + (x - 5)(x - 4)(x - 3)(x + 4) + x(x + 1)(x - 5)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 - 8*x^3 - 18*x^2 + 94*x - 210"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x - 3)(x + 3)(x + 5) + (x - 1)(x - 5)(x + 3) + (x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 + 5*x^3 - 37*x^2 - 49*x + 124"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x - 2)(x + 2) + x(x - 1)(x - 3)(x + 3) + x(x - 1)(x - 5)(x + 2)(x + 3) + (x + 1)(x + 3)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^5 + x^4 - 18*x^3 - 15*x^2 + 58*x + 15"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x - 2) + (x + 2)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "2*x^2 + 3*x + 10"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 4)(x - 2) + (x + 1)(x + 3)(x + 4)(x + 5) + (x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 5) + x(x + 1)(x - 1)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 + 3*x^3 + 113*x^2 + 24*x + 80"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 5)(x + 2) + x(x + 1)(x - 3)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 3*x^3 - 13*x^2 - 25*x - 10"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 4) + x(x + 4)(x + 5) + (x + 1)(x + 3)(x + 4) + (x - 1)(x - 4)(x - 2)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 6*x^4 - 8*x^3 + 106*x^2 - 27*x + 4"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 5)(x - 2)(x + 2) + x(x + 2)(x + 5) + x(x - 3)(x + 3)(x + 5) + x(x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 3)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 4*x^4 - 16*x^3 - 24*x^2 + 57*x"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 5)(x - 3)(x + 5) + x(x + 1)(x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 5*x^4 - 4*x^3 - 41*x^2 + 63*x"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x - 5)(x + 3) + (x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 2)(x + 5) + (x - 1)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 + 2*x^3 - 27*x^2 - 14*x + 5"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 5)(x + 4) + x(x - 5)(x + 2)(x + 4) + (x - 4)(x - 3)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 2*x^3 - 21*x^2 - 68*x - 8"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x - 5)(x - 4) + (x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 2) + x(x - 1)(x - 4)(x - 3)",
    "answer": "3*x^4 - 24*x^3 + 39*x^2 + 46*x - 40"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 1)(x + 3) + x(x + 3)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "2*x^3 + 11*x^2 + 14*x - 3"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x - 4) + x(x + 2)(x + 4) + x(x - 1)(x + 2) + (x - 1)(x - 2)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "3*x^3 + 8*x^2 - 6*x + 10"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 5)(x - 2) + x(x + 1)(x - 4)(x - 2)",
    "answer": "x^4 - 5*x^3 + 3*x^2 + x + 10"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x + 3) + (x - 4)(x + 2)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "2*x^3 + 3*x^2 - 17*x - 24"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 4)(x - 2) + x(x - 5)(x - 2)(x + 5) + x(x - 2)(x + 3)(x + 5) + x(x - 1)(x - 4)(x - 2)",
    "answer": "3*x^4 - 3*x^3 - 11*x^2 + 6*x + 8"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 2)(x + 5) + x(x - 1)(x - 5)(x + 3)(x + 4) + (x - 3)(x + 2)(x + 3)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 2*x^4 - 18*x^3 - 34*x^2 - x - 82"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 2)(x + 3) + (x - 2)(x + 4) + x(x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 3) + x(x - 4)(x - 3)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "x^5 + x^4 - 17*x^3 - 7*x^2 + 79*x - 2"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 5)(x - 3) + (x + 1)(x - 5)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "x^3 - 25*x"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x + 2)(x + 5) + x(x - 4)(x - 3) + (x - 4)(x + 2) + x(x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 + 10*x^3 - 7*x^2 - 12*x - 8"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x - 4)(x + 4) + (x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^4 - 17*x^2 + 2*x + 24"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x + 5) + (x + 1)(x - 2)(x + 5) + (x - 1)(x - 4)(x + 3) + (x + 1)(x - 1)",
    "answer": "2*x^3 + 4*x^2 - 12*x + 6"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 5)(x + 2) + x(x + 1)(x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 2) + x(x - 4)(x - 2) + (x - 1)(x - 5)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 3*x^4 - 5*x^3 + x + 15"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 2)(x + 3) + x(x - 5)(x + 2)",
    "answer": "2*x^3 + 2*x^2 - 4*x"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 2)(x + 4)(x + 5) + x(x - 5)(x - 2) + (x + 1)(x - 4)(x + 2)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 + 11*x^3 - 11*x^2 - 66*x - 64"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 2)(x + 5) + (x + 1)(x - 3) + x(x - 4)(x - 3) + x(x + 2)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "2*x^3 + 23*x + 7"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 3) + x(x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 2)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 - 8*x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 4)(x + 2)(x + 5) + (x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 4*x^3 - 23*x^2 - 56*x + 80"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 5)(x - 3)(x + 2)(x + 5) + x(x - 1)(x + 2)(x + 4)(x + 5) + x(x - 5)(x - 2) + x(x + 1)(x + 2)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 12*x^4 + 35*x^3 - 19*x^2 + 5*x + 150"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 5)(x - 2)(x + 5) + x(x - 1)(x - 4)(x + 2)",
    "answer": "x^4 - 2*x^3 - 8*x^2 - 17*x + 50"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x - 4)(x - 2) + (x + 1)(x - 4)(x - 3)(x + 5) + x(x - 5)(x + 2)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 - 5*x^3 - 26*x^2 + 35*x + 60"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 3)(x + 4) + x(x + 1)(x - 4)(x - 3)(x + 4) + (x + 1)(x - 5)(x + 3)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^5 - x^4 - 16*x^3 + 12*x^2 - 34*x - 72"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 2)(x + 3) + x(x + 1)(x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 2) + x(x - 5)(x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "2*x^5 - 7*x^4 - 29*x^3 + 47*x^2 + 121*x - 6"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 5)(x + 5) + (x + 1)(x + 4) + (x + 1)(x - 1)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "2*x^3 + 4*x^2 - 21*x + 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x + 3) + (x - 1)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "2*x^2 + 7*x - 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 3)(x + 2)(x + 3)(x + 4) + x(x - 4)(x + 2)(x + 4)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "2*x^5 + 13*x^4 - 7*x^3 - 166*x^2 - 232*x"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x + 2) + (x - 1)(x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 3) + x(x + 1)(x + 3) + (x + 3)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 4*x^3 + x^2 + 4*x + 24"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 3)(x + 4)(x + 5) + (x - 1)(x - 2)(x + 4)(x + 5) + (x + 1)(x - 3)(x + 3)(x + 5) + (x + 1)(x - 2)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 + 14*x^3 + x^2 - 110*x - 75"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x - 2) + x(x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 3)(x + 2)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 7*x^4 + 5*x^3 + 32*x^2 - 33*x + 2"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x - 5) + x(x - 1)(x - 5)(x + 2) + x(x + 1)(x - 1) + (x - 4)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^4 - 2*x^3 - 10*x^2 + 5*x - 20"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x - 4)(x - 2) + (x + 1)(x + 3)(x + 4)(x + 5) + x(x - 5)(x + 2)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 + 7*x^3 + 70*x^2 + 89*x + 60"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x - 5) + (x + 1)(x - 1)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^3 + 6*x^2 - 7*x"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x + 2)(x + 3) + (x + 1)(x - 2)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 6*x^3 + 12*x^2 + 5*x - 2"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 3)(x + 3)(x + 4)(x + 5) + x(x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^5 + x^4 - 11*x^3 + 11*x^2 - 17*x - 180"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x - 4)(x + 2) + (x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 - 8*x^3 - 27*x^2 + 133*x - 100"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x - 5)(x + 2) + x(x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 4) + (x + 1)(x - 4)(x - 2) + (x + 1)(x + 3)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 - 12*x^3 + 25*x^2 + 11*x + 20"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 4)(x - 3) + x(x - 1)(x - 3)",
    "answer": "x^4 - 6*x^3 + 7*x^2 + 10*x - 12"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 3)(x + 5) + x(x - 4)(x - 2)",
    "answer": "x^3 - 5*x^2 + 10*x - 15"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x - 2)(x + 3) + x(x + 1)(x - 5)(x - 3)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 3*x^4 - 12*x^3 + 31*x^2 + 39*x"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 5)(x - 3) + (x + 1)(x - 3)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "2*x^3 - 7*x^2 + 6*x - 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x - 2)(x + 4)(x + 5) + (x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 2)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 7*x^3 - 7*x^2 - 43*x + 42"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 3)(x + 3) + (x - 1)(x - 4)(x + 3)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 3*x^3 - 19*x^2 - 41*x + 48"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 5)(x - 4)(x - 2) + x(x + 1)(x - 5)(x + 3)(x + 4) + (x - 5)(x + 2)(x + 4)(x + 5) + (x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 3)(x - 2)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 6*x^4 - 37*x^3 - 21*x^2 - 311*x - 170"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 3) + x(x - 4)(x + 2)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 6*x^4 + x^3 + 51*x^2 - 92*x"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x - 2)(x + 2) + x(x - 4)(x + 2)(x + 3)(x + 5) + x(x + 1)(x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 2)",
    "answer": "2*x^5 + 5*x^4 - 17*x^3 - 90*x^2 - 104*x"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x - 5) + x(x - 1)(x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 5) + (x + 3)(x + 5) + (x + 1)(x + 2)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 4*x^4 - 7*x^3 - 13*x^2 + 50*x + 25"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 5) + (x - 2)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 5*x^3 - 3*x^2 - 17*x - 10"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 3)(x + 2)(x + 4)(x + 5) + (x - 4)(x + 2) + x(x + 1)(x + 4) + x(x - 3)(x + 2)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 + 11*x^3 + 2*x^2 - 90*x - 128"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 5)(x - 2) + x(x - 5)(x - 2) + (x - 3)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^3 - 5*x^2 + 4*x - 2"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 2)(x + 5) + (x - 1)(x + 3) + x(x + 1)(x + 2)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 7*x^3 + 16*x^2 + 13*x - 13"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x - 4)(x + 2)(x + 4) + x(x + 1)(x - 4) + (x - 3)(x + 3)(x + 4) + x(x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 + 2*x^3 - 31*x^2 - 5*x - 4"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 5) + x(x - 5)(x - 4)(x - 3)(x + 2) + x(x - 1)(x + 2)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "2*x^5 - 14*x^4 + 6*x^3 + 160*x^2 - 226*x"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 3) + x(x - 4)(x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 3) + x(x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 5) + x(x - 5)(x + 4)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 3*x^4 + 6*x^3 + 6*x^2 - 148*x - 12"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x + 2) + (x - 5)(x - 2)",
    "answer": "x^3 + 2*x^2 - 9*x + 10"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 3)(x + 3) + (x - 1)(x + 2)(x + 3)(x + 5) + (x - 1)(x - 5)(x + 5) + (x + 1)(x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 + 11*x^3 - 3*x^2 - 17*x + 35"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x - 2)(x + 4) + x(x - 1)(x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 3) + (x - 1)(x - 4)(x - 2)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 3*x^4 - 5*x^3 + 17*x^2 - 2*x - 8"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 2)(x + 2) + x(x + 1)(x - 3)",
    "answer": "x^3 - x^2 - 3*x - 4"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x + 3)(x + 5) + x(x + 1)(x + 3)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 + 15*x^3 + 26*x^2 - 3*x"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 2) + (x - 5)(x + 2)",
    "answer": "x^4 - 3*x^3 - 7*x^2 + 9*x + 6"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 5)(x - 3)(x + 3) + x(x - 5)(x - 2)(x + 2) + x(x - 1)(x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 2)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 3*x^4 - 10*x^3 + 7*x^2 + 49*x"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 1)(x + 4)(x + 5) + (x + 1)(x - 5)(x - 4) + x(x - 3)(x + 4)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 + 16*x^3 + 4*x^2 - 58*x"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 3)(x + 4) + (x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "x^5 + x^4 - 12*x^3 - 4*x^2 + 2*x + 24"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 2)(x + 3)(x + 4)(x + 5) + x(x - 5)(x - 3)(x + 3)(x + 5) + x(x - 4)(x + 2)(x + 3) + x(x - 5)(x - 2)(x + 3)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "3*x^5 + 15*x^4 + 11*x^3 + 126*x^2 + 441*x"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 3)(x + 3) + (x + 1)(x - 4)(x - 3)(x + 2) + (x - 3)(x - 2)",
    "answer": "x^4 - 4*x^3 - 5*x^2 + 17*x + 21"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 4)(x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 3) + (x - 1)(x - 2)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^4 - 5*x^3 + x^2 + 41*x - 62"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 3)(x + 2)(x + 4)(x + 5) + (x - 1)(x - 3) + x(x - 1)(x - 4)(x + 3)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 4*x^4 - 13*x^3 - 37*x^2 - 18*x - 117"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 2)(x + 5) + x(x - 2)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "2*x^3 + 9*x^2 + 2*x"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x - 2) + x(x - 1)(x - 3)(x + 5) + x(x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 3)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "x^5 + x^4 - 8*x^3 - 20*x^2 + 26*x"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 4)(x + 2)(x + 4) + (x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 4*x^3 - 11*x^2 - 52*x - 44"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x - 3)(x + 2)(x + 3) + (x - 1)(x + 2)(x + 4)(x + 5) + x(x - 1)(x - 5)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 5*x^4 + x^3 - 19*x^2 + 4*x - 40"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 2) + (x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 5) + x(x + 1)(x - 2)",
    "answer": "2*x^3 - 4*x^2 - 28*x + 98"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 3)(x + 4) + x(x - 4)(x + 2)(x + 3) + (x + 1)(x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 + 2*x^3 - 28*x^2 - 26*x + 24"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 2)(x + 2) + (x - 5)(x - 2)(x + 3)(x + 4) + (x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 4)",
    "answer": "x^4 + x^3 - 36*x^2 + 15*x + 96"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x - 4)(x + 2)(x + 3) + (x + 1)(x - 4)(x + 3)(x + 5) + x(x - 5)(x + 2)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "3*x^4 + 5*x^3 - 47*x^2 - 117*x - 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x + 3) + (x + 1)(x - 2)(x + 2)",
    "answer": "2*x^3 + 5*x^2 - x - 4"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 2) + x(x + 1)(x - 5) + (x - 5)(x - 4)(x - 3)",
    "answer": "x^4 - 5*x^3 - 14*x^2 + 82*x - 60"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 3)(x + 2) + x(x - 4)(x - 2) + x(x + 1)(x - 4)(x + 2)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 3*x^4 - 12*x^3 - 55*x^2 - 30*x"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x - 4) + (x - 4)(x + 3)(x + 4)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 9*x^3 - 6*x^2 - 124*x - 240"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 2)(x + 2) + (x + 1)(x - 3) + (x - 2)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^4 - 3*x^2 - 7"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x - 5)(x - 3)(x + 3) + (x + 1)(x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 4) + (x - 2)(x + 2)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 3*x^4 - 18*x^3 + 16*x^2 + 109*x + 76"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x - 2) + (x - 3)(x + 5) + x(x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 5) + x(x + 1)(x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "x^5 - x^4 - 17*x^3 - 9*x^2 + 123*x - 13"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 3)(x + 2) + (x - 1)(x - 4)(x - 3)(x + 4) + x(x - 1)(x - 3)(x + 2)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "2*x^5 - 3*x^4 - 14*x^3 - x^2 + 64*x - 48"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 4)(x + 4) + x(x + 1)(x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 2) + (x - 1)(x + 4) + x(x - 5)(x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "2*x^5 - 4*x^4 - 31*x^3 + 18*x^2 + 83*x - 20"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x + 4) + (x - 4)(x - 2)(x + 3)(x + 5) + x(x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 2)(x + 2) + (x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 2)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 4*x^4 - 26*x^2 + 7*x + 284"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x - 3)(x + 5) + (x - 1)(x - 5)(x + 5) + (x + 1)(x + 2)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 5*x^3 - 7*x^2 - 26*x + 33"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 5) + x(x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 5) + (x - 5)(x + 4)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 5*x^4 - 19*x^3 + 124*x^2 - 126*x - 95"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 4)(x + 3) + (x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 4) + x(x - 1)(x - 5)(x + 2) + (x - 1)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "x^4 - 2*x^3 - 11*x^2 - 17*x + 65"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 4)(x + 5) + x(x + 1)(x + 3) + (x + 1)(x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 2)",
    "answer": "x^4 - x^3 - 2*x^2 + 12*x - 8"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 5)(x - 3)(x + 3)(x + 4) + (x - 5)(x - 2)(x + 4)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 + x^3 - 62*x^2 - 41*x + 380"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 4)(x + 5) + x(x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 3) + (x + 1)(x - 4)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 12*x^3 + 2*x^2 + 29*x + 4"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 4)(x + 4) + x(x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 5*x^4 - 12*x^3 + 82*x^2 - 56*x"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 4)(x + 5) + (x - 3)(x + 5) + (x + 1)(x + 2)(x + 5) + x(x - 1)(x - 3)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 2*x^3 + 5*x^2 + 51*x - 5"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 2)(x + 3) + x(x + 3)(x + 5) + x(x + 1)(x - 5)(x + 2)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "x^5 + x^4 - 18*x^3 - 40*x^2 - 14*x - 6"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 3)(x + 2) + x(x - 1)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "x^4 - 6*x^3 + 7*x^2 + 28*x - 30"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 5)(x - 3)(x + 4) + (x - 2)(x + 3) + (x - 3)(x - 2)",
    "answer": "x^4 - 3*x^3 - 19*x^2 + 39*x + 60"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 2)(x + 5) + x(x - 4)(x + 3)(x + 5) + x(x + 1)(x - 3)(x + 3)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 6*x^4 - x^3 - 61*x^2 - 93*x - 10"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 2)(x + 3)(x + 4)(x + 5) + (x - 3)(x + 4) + (x - 3)(x - 2)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 10*x^4 + 23*x^3 - 32*x^2 - 124*x - 6"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 3)(x + 5) + (x - 2)(x + 3) + x(x - 1)(x - 2)(x + 5) + (x + 1)(x - 4)(x + 4)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "2*x^4 + 8*x^3 - 22*x^2 - 83*x - 101"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 3)(x - 2)(x + 4) + (x - 4)(x - 2) + (x - 5)(x + 2)(x + 3)(x + 5) + (x - 5)(x - 2)(x + 2)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "3*x^4 + 3*x^3 - 56*x^2 - 103*x - 62"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x + 1)(x - 3)(x + 2)(x + 3) + x(x - 5)(x - 3) + x(x + 1)(x - 5)(x + 2)(x + 3) + (x - 5)(x + 2)(x + 3)(x + 4)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 3*x^4 - 11*x^3 - 83*x^2 - 148*x - 138"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x + 2)(x + 3) + (x - 2)(x + 2) + (x + 1)(x - 1)(x - 4) + (x - 5)(x - 4)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 7*x^3 + 9*x^2 - 4*x + 20"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x + 1)(x - 4)(x + 5) + x(x - 1)(x + 2)(x + 3)(x + 5)",
    "answer": "x^5 + 10*x^4 + 23*x^3 - 20*x^2 - 50*x"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify (x - 1)(x + 2) + x(x + 1)(x - 1)(x + 3)",
    "answer": "x^4 + 3*x^3 - 2*x - 2"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x - 5)(x - 2)(x + 2) + x(x - 5)(x - 3) + (x - 4)(x + 3)(x + 5) + (x - 4)(x + 2)",
    "answer": "x^5 - 6*x^4 + 3*x^3 + 21*x^2 - 24*x - 68"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand and simplify x(x - 1)(x - 5) + (x - 2)(x + 2)",
    "answer": "x^3 - 5*x^2 + 5*x - 4"
  }
]